<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Spatial inequalities</title>
    <link>https://example.com/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Spatial inequalities</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 10:49:34 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Research team</title>
      <link>https://example.com/projects/research-team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 19:27:37 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/projects/research-team/</guid>
      <description>Nikos Patias Nikos Patias is a PhD student at the Geographic Data Science Lab at the University of Liverpool. He is currently working as a Policy Analyst at the Centre for Entrepreneurship, SMEs, Regions and Cities of the OECD. His research interests are: computational urban science, spatial inequalities and Geographic Information Science.
Contact N.Patias@liverpool.ac.uk
patnik.github.io
@pat_nikos
Dr. Francisco Rowe Francisco Rowe is a Senior Lecturer in Human Quantitative Geography at the Department of Geography and Planning within the University of Liverpool, lead of the Geographic Data Science Lab.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>extRatum</title>
      <link>https://example.com/projects/r-package/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 10:49:34 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/projects/r-package/</guid>
      <description>An R package that calculates summary indices for built environment characteristics.
Overview extRatum is a package used to provide summary statistics of local geospatial features within a given geographic area. It does so by calculating the area covered by a target geospatial feature (i.e. buildings, parks, lakes, etc.). The geospatial features can be of any type of geospatial data, including point, polygon or line data. For examples of extRatum functionalities follow this link and for the package website this link.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactive maps</title>
      <link>https://example.com/projects/interactive-maps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 10:48:58 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/projects/interactive-maps/</guid>
      <description> Temporal neighbourhood classification 1971-2011 Access here   Neighbourhood trajectories 1971-2011 Access here   Sustainable Urban Development Index (SUDI) Access here  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Media</title>
      <link>https://example.com/projects/media/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 10:48:49 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/projects/media/</guid>
      <description>CARTO Map of The Month: Trajectories of Neighbourhood Change Read the article here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Data Products</title>
      <link>https://example.com/projects/open-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 10:48:38 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/projects/open-data/</guid>
      <description>The outputs of the trajectories of neighbourhood socioeconomic change in Great Britain (197-2011) can be downloaded as a geopackage from CDRC website here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Policy Briefs</title>
      <link>https://example.com/projects/policy-briefs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 10:48:10 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/projects/policy-briefs/</guid>
      <description>Rowe, F., Patias, N., and Arribas-Bel, D. (2020). Policy brief: Neighbourhood change and trajectories of inequality in britain, 1971-2011 Access here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Journal articles</title>
      <link>https://example.com/projects/articles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 09:49:22 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/projects/articles/</guid>
      <description>Patias, N., Rowe, F., and Cavazzi, S. (2020). A scalable analytical framework for spatio-temporal analysis of neighborhood change: A sequence analysis approach. Geospatial Technologies for Local and Regional Development, pages 223–241 https://doi.org/10.1007/978-3-030-14745-7_13
Patias, N., Rowe, F. and Arribas-Bel, D. (2021), Trajectories of neighbourhood inequality in Britain: Unpacking inter-regional socioeconomic imbalances, 1971-2011. The Geographical Journal. Accepted Author Manuscript. https://doi.org/10.1111/geoj.12420
Patias, N., Rowe, F., Cavazzi, S., and Arribas-Bel, D. (2021). Sustainable urban development indicators in Great Britain from 2001 to 2016.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
